(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T17:07:52.660051",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
うさぎ the MEGAMI!!
[Usagi the MEGAMI!! - 1st Usada Pekora Solo Live]
ファースト！うさぎのぺこライブ！ うさぎざめがみにご来場いただき、
First! Welcome to Usada Pekora's first live, Usada The Megami,
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
あーりぺこー！
Aripeko!
わー！
Yay!
かんぺこかんぺこ、かんぺこ！
Kampeko, kampeko, kampeko!
本日のライブ開催な、うさだぺこーらぺこんと
Today's live is brought to you by Usada Pekora, pekon and...
おももおもー！
Omomoomo!
ねえ、あんたたちさ、すげえ笑顔でカメラから切り抜かれてんだじゃん。ぺこらもなんかニコニコしちゃった、さすがにね、なんかさ、いーって感じで切り抜かれてるのをみて
Hey, you guys, you're getting cut on camera with huge smiles. Even Pekora smiled, seeing you guys looking all grin-y...
そんなね、みんなに最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかぺこらからご案内させていただきますぺこん！
So, to ensure everyone enjoys the live until the very end, Pekora has a few announcements for you, pekon!
キャハハハ！
Kyahahaha!
お、いいよ！声出てるね！ 今日頼むぞマジで！
Oh, nice! You guys are using your voices! Count on you today for real!
うおおお！
Whoa!
じゃあ行くね。公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたしております。
Here we go. Photography, audio recording, and video recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
また、本公演は避難誘導等の音頭を行います。万が一避難が必要になった
Also, during this performance, we will lead evacuation guidance. In the unlikely event that evacuation becomes necessary,
場合は、すぐに非常灯を点灯しますので、スタッフの指示に従ってください。
emergency lights will turn on immediately, so please follow the staff's instructions.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまったときは、無理せずスタッフへ知らせてほしいぺこん。
In the unlikely event you feel unwell, please don't push yourself and let a staff member know, pekon.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、カタ車、ステージ上に物を投げ込む、ステージ上に上がる、規制を上げる、前に押し寄せるなどの
Mosh pits, crowdsurfing, cartwheels, throwing objects onto the stage, getting on stage, raising restrictions, surging forward, and other
過激な応援行為、カドないジャンプ行為などは、他のみんなの迷惑になる公演を妨げる危険行為は一切禁止です。ルールを守って盛り上がってほしいぺこん！
extreme cheering behaviors, dangerous jumps, and dangerous acts that disrupt the performance and bother others are strictly prohibited. Please follow the rules and get hyped, pekon!
そして、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, for this performance, cameras for video streaming and photography will enter the venue, and audience seating may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がございま...可能性がございますので、あらかじめごりょうし...ご了承ください。
These images and photos may be used for promotions, so please be aware of this in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは「うさめがぺこら」です。ハッシュタグを使ってたくさんたくさん盛り上げてほしいぺこーん！
Also, the live hashtag is "#UsamegaPekora". Please use the hashtag to hype it up a lot, pekoon!
うおおおー！
Whoa!
なんか今のお前たちの声だったら、もうしょっぱなから盛り上がれる気がするわ。
Hearing your voices just now makes me feel like we can get hyped right from the start.
頼んだよ、お前たちー！
I'm counting on you guys!
それでは、開演までもう少し！みんな盛り上がる準備できてるー！
Well then, just a little longer until the show starts! Is everyone ready to get hyped?!
ほんなら、じゃあライブでまたね！
Alright then, see you at the live!
ぺこむら！ぺこむら！ぺこむら！
Pekomura! Pekomura! Pekomura!
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ ご褒美 ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, reward, lavie chu,
噛み付いて 骨 まで チュッチュッチュッ
Bite down to the bone, chu-chu-chu!
バット 煽っ て ない の ? えっ ?
Batting an eye, aren't you? Huh?
おつかれ 今日 も ノー ダメージ
Good work today, zero damage!
ズバッ と 威張っ て たい の ! ね ?
Wanting to act high and mighty, right? Huh?
笑える ほど に 弱虫 よ
Cowardly enough to make you smile,
踊る ばか ばか ばか
Dancing foolishly,
無駄 ね ほらほら
It's useless, look, look!
ごめん ちょっと タイムナァ
Sorry, just a timeout.
大草原
Big grassland!
やばめ ドキドキ
Oh no, my heart is pounding!
本音 ラッキー ラッキー
True feelings, lucky lucky!
マネジメント ナンバー
Management number,
無能 無能 無能 意味 の アンマッチ
Useless, useless, useless, meaningless mismatch!
無能 無能 無能 過度 に 反対
Useless, useless, useless, overly opposed!
無能 無能 無能 ゴミ も 同様
Useless, useless, useless, equivalent to trash!
無能 無能 無能 ワンパン
Useless, useless, useless, one-punch!
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ ご褒美 ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, reward, lavie chu,
あなた じゃ 話 に なん ない 平凡
Nothing to talk about, how mediocre.
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ 下等 ね ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, bottom tier, hey, lavie chu,
噛み付いて 骨 まで チュッチュッチュッ
Bite down to the bone, chu-chu-chu!
声 を 頂戴 涙 頂戴
Receive my voice, receive my tears,
ヤミーヤミー ヤミー
Yamyamyamy,
声 を 頂戴 涙 頂戴
Receive my voice, receive my tears,
ラヴィラヴィラヴィ
Lavie lavie lavie!
弱音 吐い て 悶え たって
Uttering faint sighs and agonizing,
無駄 で 無駄 で 愚か さ すら 気付け ない よ ね
Useless, useless, you don't even realize how foolish it is!
喉 渇い て 血 を 含ん で
Throat parched, holding blood in your mouth,
悪い 悪い 顔 で 笑う
Smiling with an evil, wicked face.
逃げ出し ちゃ だめ だめ
Don't run away, no no!
手 に 入れろ 勢い 出し て
Get it with all your might!
バカ だろ おまえ まじ で
You idiot, seriously,
この 傷 ばいか しね
This injury becomes you.
窮地 から 這いずり回っ て
Stumbling around from this desperate plight,
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ 絞っ て ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, squeeze it out, lavie chu,
断末魔 の 叫び と 忠誠 を
The apocalyptic screams and loyalty!
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ 卑劣 の ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, despicable lavie chu,
奪い取れ 命 を
Take back your life!
チュッチュッチュッチュッ
Chu-chu-chu-chu!
逃げ出し ちゃ だめ 枯れ出し ちゃ だめ
Don't run away, don't wither away,
ヤミーヤミー ヤミー
Yamyamyamy,
逃げ出し ちゃ だめ 枯れ出し ちゃ だめ
Don't run away, don't wither away,
ラヴィラヴィラヴィ
Lavie lavie lavie!
無能 無能 無能 意味 の アンマッチ
Useless, useless, useless, meaningless mismatch!
無能 無能 無能 過度 に 反対
Useless, useless, useless, overly opposed!
無能 無能 無能 ゴミ も 同様
Useless, useless, useless, equivalent to trash!
無能 無能 無能 ワンパン
Useless, useless, useless, one-punch!
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ ご褒美 ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, reward, lavie chu,
あなた じゃ 話 に なん ない 平凡
Nothing to talk about, how mediocre.
ラヴィラヴィ チュウ 下等 ね ラヴィ チュウ
Lavie lavie chu, bottom tier, hey, lavie chu,
噛み付いて 骨 まで チュッチュッチュッ
Bite down to the bone, chu-chu-chu!
声 を 頂戴 涙 頂戴
Receive my voice, receive my tears,
ヤミーヤミー ヤミー
Yamyamyamy,
声 を 頂戴 涙 頂戴
Receive my voice, receive my tears,
ラヴィラヴィラヴィ
Lavie lavie lavie!
美音 どかげ で 無理 げ と と - どちら も クリア が 見え ませ ん
So cute, so arrogant, impossible and impossible,
暴走 しょ 状態 以上 は 好き アイテム は どこ で 買え ます か ?
Rampaging state, well, that's fine, but
最初 説明 と だない 見え ない の は 私 の アイエムピー ?
First explanation, there's no future in lying,
魔法 マンション も 超え て やる けど 前 に 誰 か いり おり ます か ?
I'll surpass even a luxury mansion, but
ちゃんと 届い てる あなた の エール
Is your love reaching you properly?
いじいじ 箱 さがり 連打 だ 失敗 も 多々 ミス の 上昇
Shivering, box sagging, rhythmic mistakes, multiple consecutive jumps!
ナッピーナッピー 小さな ビット で でかい 世界 よく 中
Nappi nappi, tiny bit, huge world right in the middle,
上手く いか ない プレイ イング メソ だって あなた と し たい
Play it smoothly, I want to be with you,
私 を 見 て て 欲しい の よ 様子 見 は し ない で ね
Don't just watch me, don't leave me alone!
無用 で も 愛し て ね もっと 飛べる から
Even if you're useless, I love you, so jump with me!
ラッピーラッピー まだまだ あなた と でかい 世界 よく 中
Lavie lavie, still more, huge world right in the middle,
ぼーっ と し ちゃっ たら 制裁 し て ね
If you doze off, I'll punish you!
だって 愛 は 日常 死き より
Because your love is pushing me hard!
てーれれー！
Let's begin!
どんなものでもくださいな
Give me whatever you want, whenever you want!
月まで届くらに届くらに配達 急のららららららび
Deliver it right to my door by tomorrow!
もっとしたいのららららららび
I want more! Lalalalalabi!
祈りなさい　願いなさい
Pray, and make a wish.
悩めるあなたたちのために
For all of you who are struggling,
今、最強女神 † ウーサペコラ が、舞い降りる
Now, the ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora, descends!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
疲れ切ってしおれたあなた野兎の
For you, worn out and exhausted,
助け呼ぶ声
a cry for help!
女神降臨 勝利の合図は
The goddess has arrived, the sign of victory!
お任せなさい！
Leave it to me!
ガミガミ怒る上司も
Even the grumpy boss,
裏じゃ兎田にぺこぺこしてる
is bowing down to Pekora behind the scenes!
もっと崇めるぺこ
Worship her more!
いくぞーーー！！！
Here we go!
ぺこーらぺこーらら　ありがとう！
Pekorapera lala, thank you!
迷える野兎おいでませ
Guide us through our bewildered days.
ぺこーらぺこーらら　ありがとう！
Pekorapera lala, thank you!
天上天下 兎田独尊
The one and only Usada reigns supreme.
ぺこーらぺこーらら　可愛いよ！
Pekorapera lala, you're so cute!
まだまだ全然聞こえません！
We still can't hear you at all!
ぺこーらぺこーらら　可愛いよ！
Pekorapera lala, you're so cute!
讃えなさい！ご唱和どうぞ！
Praise her! Sing along with her!
ぺこら！ぺこら！ぺこら！ぺこら！
Pekora! Pekora! Pekora! Pekora!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora,
兎田の華咲かせましょう
let's make Usada's flower bloom!
世界一のどうもどうも
Hello to the whole world,
兎田ぺこらここにあり
Usada Pekora is here!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora,
兎田の意地見せましょう
let's show Usada's spite!
どんちゃん騒ぎパリラ　レラ
Let's go wild, party lala!
あなたもあなたもあなたたちみんな
You, you, and all of you,
さあ行こう！
let's go!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
ぺこらの配信は？
What's Pekora's stream?
てんさーい！
Genius!
ぺこらの実況は？
What's Pekora's let's play?
せいかーい！
Spot-on!
ぺこらの寝言は？
What's Pekora's bedtime story?
ウサ耳立てて飛び跳ねろ！
Open your rabbit ears and dance away!
ぺこらぺこらぺこらぺこら
Pekora pekora pekora pekora
ぺこらぺこら
Pekora pekora
あなたたち！
All of you!
やるぺこじゃん！
You can do it!
ぺこーらぺこーら　ありがとう！
Thank you, Pekora!
もっともっと大きな声で！
Louder, louder!
ぺこーらぺこーら　ありがとう！
Thank you, Pekora!
最終鬼畜兎教官
The ultimate brutal rabbit drill instructor,
今でも十分可愛いやろ！？
is still plenty cute, right?
崇めなさい！ご唱和どうぞ！
Worship her! Sing along with her!
ぺこら！ぺこら！ぺこら！ぺこら！
Pekora! Pekora! Pekora! Pekora!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora,
兎田の星目指しましょう
let's aim for Usada's star!
宇宙一のどうもどうも
Hello to the whole universe,
兎田ぺこら大勝利！
Usada Pekora's big victory!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora,
兎田の道極めましょう yeah
let's master Usada's path, yeah!
うさぎ the megami 開幕だ！
Rabbit The Goddess opening now!
あなたもあなたもあなたたちみんな
You, you, and all of you,
ぺこらの行き着く先は一体…！？
let's find out what's ahead!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
ウサ耳立てて飛び跳ねろ！
Rabbit-eared wings to fly away!
ぺこらぺこらぺこらぺこら
Pekora pekora pekora pekora
ぺこらぺこら
Pekora pekora
あなたたち！
All of you!
やるぺこじゃん！
You can do it!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
最強！ 最強！
Strongest! Strongest!
最強女神 † ウーサペコラ！
The ultimate goddess, Usa-Pekora!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あなたたちの愛どる
Thank you for all your love,
さいおわピー！
it's finally over!
りりやい！
Thank you!
ラララ、ララ！
Lalala, lala!
出会えたね 嬉しいね
Meeting you was so wonderful.
街灯りくぐって 足をぱたぱたしながら 今日を楽しみにで
Let's make today special, stepping to the rhythm.
ねねの顔だよ！
Hey, hey, can you hear my heart beating?
緊張なんかしちゃってる場合じゃないっと
If you're feeling nervous, that's okay,
一秒無駄になんてできないさあ始めましょう
we can't afford to waste even a single second!
旅立とう 冒険 そして インドア の 神話 へ ――
Embarking on an adventure and stepping into an indoor myth—
最大級 の ラララララ ラビット ！！
The greatest, ultimate,ララララ Rabbit!!
最序盤 の スライム に ビビる の が 大概 な マイライフ （ なんだこれ は ！）
Getting scared by the very first slime is pretty much my my-life (What is this?!)
ワン ・ トゥ ・ スリー で 繋がっ た セカイ に 愛 が あふれだす （ ラララララ ヴィ ！）
In a world connected 1-2-3, love overflows (Lalalarala vi!)
8bit に 感じる ドキドキ
A pounding feeling in 8-bit,
2D の ラブ じゃ だめ です か ？！
Isn't 2D love good too?
運ゲー 状態 ぶざけい じゃ ない ぞ
This isn't just Gacha luck acting up,
レベルアップ し て 超え て やる あ ！
I'll level up and blow right past it!
夢 に 見 てる ファンファーレ の 音 乱数調整 一転攻勢 一点突破 想定外 も ロマンス の 過程 ――
The fan-favorite tune I see in my dreams, randomized adjustments, instant offensive shift, point breakthrough, unexpected romance process...
ラヴィ ラヴィ ちいさな ビート で でっかい アイ を 交信 中 ！
Lavi-lavi, tiny beat with a giant eye, exchanging signals right now!
ちょっと 沼っ て も 許し て ね ？ いつだって 愛 は 非効率 ！ （ でしょ ？！ ）
Forgive me if I get a bit hooked, after all, love is so inefficient! (Right?)
jumpin ' jumpin ' 跳ねる ハート を 捕まえ て おい て ね ！
Jumpin' jumpin', catch that bouncing heart and hold on tight!
二兎 なんて 追わ ない で トゥルールエンド に なる まで
Don't chase two hares, until we reach the true end.
最大級 の ラララララ ラビット ！！ （ love ビート ！！ ）
The greatest, ultimate,ララララ Rabbit!! (Love beat!!)
人生 と かけ て 無理 ゲー と 解く どちらも クリア が みえ ませ ん ！！
Treating life like an impossible game, neither of us can see the clear screen!
この ラブ っ て 状態 異常 を とく アイテム は どこ で 買え ます か ？！
This "love" status abnormality, where can I buy items for it?!
救済 も ！ 説明 も ！ 足り ない ！ クソゲー ！！
Rescue? Explanation? Not enough! This crappy game!!
いや 、 足り ない の 私 の イント ？！
Well, is that not enough for my INT?!
まあ 、 どんな 難所 も 超え て やる けど そのまえ に 誰か いい 案 あり ます か ？！
Well, I'll overcome any hard spot, but does anyone have a good idea before that?
ちゃんと 届い て いる あなた の エール
Your applause reaching you properly—
一進一退 八方塞がり 絶体絶命 大失敗 も サクセス の 序章 ――
One step forward, one step back, surrounded on all sides, dire strait, major failure, the prelude to success...
ラヴィ ラヴィ ちいさな ビート で でっかい セカイ 躍進 中
Lavi-lavi, tiny beat with a giant world, advancing in full force!
うまくいかない プレイング 迷走 だって あなた と し たい
A clumsy playthrough, but I want to be with you.
私 を 見て て ほしい の よそ見 は しない で ね 不器用 で も 愛し て ね もっと 跳べる から
Watch me, don't look away, love me even if I'm clumsy because I'll jump even higher!
ラヴィ ラヴィ まだまだ あなた と でっかい アイ を 更新 中 ！
Lavi-lavi, still updating a giant eye with you!
暴走 し て ちっ たら 制し て ね ？ だット 愛 は 非常識 ！！ （ ラヴィ ！）
If I start going wild, please stop me? After all, love is madness! (Lavi!)
もっともっと 跳ね て たい から ずっと そば で 見 ていて ね ！
I want to keep jumping more and more, so please keep watching by my side!
どんな 想い でも ください な 月 まで 届く くらい に
No matter what feelings they are, reach as high as the moon!
最大級 の ラララララ ラビット ！！
The greatest, ultimate,ララララ Rabbit!!
もっと し たい の ！！ ラララララ ラビット ！！ （ love ビート ！！ ）
I want to do it more! Lalalarala Rabbit!! (Love beat!!)
ファースト うさだぺこら いぶ ！！
First Usada Pekora Live!
うさぎ の メガミ に き て くれ て ありがとう ペコリーノ ！！
Welcome to Usagi the Megami!
あんた たち の 声 めちゃめちゃ 聞こえ た よ ！！
Can you all hear me loud and clear?!
会場 響き渡っ て た くらい に すごく ここん と あった に ありがとう 嬉しい よ ！！
The venue's vibe was just incredible, thank you so much for an amazing time! I'm so happy!
本当に 広い ！ いや ほら 見え てる よ ！ おー 見え てる よ ！！
It's truly huge! Man, I can see you all! I can see you!
一人一人の こと も 見え てる よ ！！ おー 見え てる よ ！！
Every single one of you, I see you!
ひろ ！ おい すごい ！ うわぁー ！！
So huge! Wow, this is amazing! Wow!
と いう こと で ついに 始まり まし た みんな ！ うさだぺこら の ソロ ライブ ！！ 気持ち は みんな どう です か ？！
So, finally, it has finally begun, everyone! Usada Pekora's solo live! How is everyone feeling?
ぺこら も 最初 は しょっぱ から みんな に もう ね ボルテージ ガセー て あげ て もらっ て 、 おぺこら も 気持ち も もう やばい ぺこ な ん です けど も 現地 ね 、 いる みんな も あったかい し 、 そして 本日 は 配信 も ね 、 やっ て いる の で コメント の みんな も どう か な
Pekora was super nervous at first, but everyone gave me a boost of energy, and Pekora was feeling great!
おー 最高 って 言っ て くれ てる よ みんな ！ ありがと う 、 ありがと う 、 ありがと う ！！
Awesome! Thank you everyone! Thank you, thank you, thank you!
そして ね 、 なんと ね 今回 の ライブ は 韓国 で も ライブ ビューイング が ね し て いる ぺこ な ん です けど も 、 韓国 の みんな 、 やばい ぜ よ ！ あんにょんはせよー ！！
And any song, you guys hype me up so much, you're the absolute best! Absolute best, absolute best!
是非 とも ね 、 よろしく お願い し ます 。 この カメラ 推し カメラ に ね 、 反映 し て おり まし た 。
Be sure to show your support, okay? Please watch over me!
いやいいか、な
I guess it's fine?
う、なんか、え、やばい、みんなやばいよ
Whoa, um... Whoa, this is bad, everyone!
み、水どうしよ、はじまっちゃった！
W-What about water? It started!
落ち着け
Calm down.
まだまだ何曲もある
There are still plenty of songs left.
落ち着けぺこだと...
Calm down, Pekora...
そしてね、今回のライブのハッシュタグ
And also, for this live's hashtag,
「うさめがぺこら」でたくさんのポストをしていただけたら
"#UsamegaPekora", if you could post lots about it,
とれんどいり、よろしくぺこだよ、おねがいれー！
Let's get it trending! Please do!
あ、すごい！
Oh, wow!
いや、まじでやばいね、あんたたちやばくない？
Seriously, this is crazy! You guys are insane!
本当にやばい！
This is seriously crazy!
ぺこらのソロライブの楽しみ方を説明しようと思ったんだけど
I thought I'd explain how to enjoy Pekora's solo live,
あんたたちもう十分できそうだけど一応伝えるね
but you guys look completely ready, though I'll tell you!
一応、みんなペンライト持ってるよね？
First off, everyone has a penlight, right?
持ってますよね？
You definitely have them, right?
ペンライトの色とか色んな色があると思うと
Penlights probably have different colors and all,
曲によって何の色にしようかなって思う方もいると
and you might wonder what color to use for certain songs,
両端にさ、こっちと...
on both sides here, this and...
ちょっと待ってね
Hold on a second.
ごめんね
Sorry.
こっち側にね、でっかいスクリーンあってさ、
On this side, there's a big screen,
ぺこらが等身大で映っててペンライトを持ってる
and Pekora is shown life-sized holding a penlight—
そのペンライトの色に合わせてもらえたらいいかなと
if you could match the color of that penlight, that'd be great.
迷ってる人はね、迷わなくてずっとやってる人も
For those hesitating, or those sticking to one color,
もしペンライト迷っている人がいたらそちらもよろしく
if anyone's hesitating on their penlight, that's there too.
あんたたちのコール、まじで最高だって！
Man, your calls are seriously the best!
この上の、ぺこらのうつや、ぴょーん！
And right up here, Pekora's... pyon!
上に表示されている歌詞やコールも歌ってほしいな
The lyrics and calls displayed up top, I want you to sing along,
でもぺこらのことずっと見ててね
but keep watching Pekora the whole time.
基本的にそうだよね、あんたたちわかってるよね？
Basically that's how it is, you guys know, right?
見るのはぺこらだからね！ほかに入れちゃダメだからね！
You're here to look at Pekora! Don't look at anyone else!
はーい、なんか気持ちいいな、今日。
Yay! Man, it feels so good today.
なんかすっごい気持ちいいな。
It feels amazingly good.
歌うやめてこのまま話そうかな、みんなと、どう？
Maybe I should stop singing and just chat, what do you think?
え、どっちの反応？それどっちの反応なの？え、いってこと？
Which reaction is that? What kind of reaction? Does that mean yes?
おお、なんか分かりづれえな、反応的に。
Oh, it's kind of hard to tell from your reactions.
歌、やめとく今日？30時間雑談するライブにしとく？
Stop singing today? Make it a 30-hour chatting live?
いや、だめぺこでしょ！
No way, that's no good, pako!
あんたたちさ、ぺこらの歌を聞きに来たぺこなんでしょ？
You guys came to listen to Pekora sing, right?
よかったわ。
Good thing.
反応なかったらどうしようかと思っちゃったぺこだけども。
I was wondering what I'd do if you didn't react.
本当に夢みたいなぺこだな、このソロライブで、ありがとね！
It's really like a dream for this solo live, thank you!
まだ緊張してるけど、最後まで楽しんでくれたら嬉しいです
I'm still nervous, but I'll be so happy if you enjoy it till the end.
YouTubeとTikTokでご覧の皆様、無料ちらみせはここまで！
To those watching on YouTube and TikTok, the free preview ends here!
いや、やだ！やだやだ、見たい見たいって！
No way! No, no, I want to see more!
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたい人は概要欄から配信サイトへ！
If you want to keep getting hyped, check the description for the stream!
それでは、みなさん！
And now, everyone!
きらなみずいろだね、本当に。
Such sparkling aquamarine, truly.
うさぎか計画のフィナーレの方へ行っておこうかなと思います。
Time to head toward the finale of the Usagika Plan.
ついにフィナーレとなるので心して聞いていただけたら
It's finally the finale, so I hope you'll listen with all your heart.
みんなでうさぎか計画を成功させるぺこ！
Let's make the Usagika Plan a success together, pako!
無料パーツは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The free portion has ended. Thank you for watching!]
無料パートは終了いたしました ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free part has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました
The free portion has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!